easyequities.co.za 2018-09-25

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                                                                  PRIVACY POLICY
                                                                                          Easy Equities
Johannesburg Office:       KZN Office:                 Directors:
T +27 (0) 87 940 6000      T +27 (0) 87 940 6090       Charles Savage/CEO
F +27 (0) 11 214 8028      F +27 (0) 31 576 5088       Gary van Dyk/CFOO
W easyequities.co.za       W easyequities.co.za
First World Trader (Pty) Ltd t/a EasyEquities is an authorised Financial Services
Provider. FSB License No. 22588.
                                                                                                        1

                                                                                                        [Privacy Policy]
                                                                                                        [Easy Equities]
TABLE OF CONTENTS
1    Protection of Personal Information Act, 2013 (POPI) ............................................................................................. 2
2    Collection of Personal Information .......................................................................................................................... 2
3    Use of Personal Information .................................................................................................................................... 2
4    Use of Cookies .......................................................................................................................................................... 4
5    Security of your Personal Information .................................................................................................................... 4
6    Changes to Statement of Privacy ............................................................................................................................ 4
7    Contact Information .................................................................................................................................................. 4
                                                                                                                                                                                 2
 PRIVACY POLICY | MAY 2014

                                                                                 [Privacy Policy]
                                                                                 [Easy Equities]
PRIVACY POLICY
EasyEquities is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and
safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Easy Equities website (the Website) and governs data
collection and usage. By using the Website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
1.    Protection of Personal Information Act, 2013 (POPI)
You acknowledge that by using the Website and by trading with Easy Equities you will be providing Easy Equities with
personal data, which may be protected by data protection legislation, including inter alia, the Protection of Personal
Information Act, 2013 (POPI). You authorise us to process all such personal data and to transmit any such personal data
to any Affiliate (which Affiliate may also process such personal data) for the purposes of performing the Contract and in
furtherance of Easy Equities legitimate interests including statistical analysis, marketing of our services and credit
control. You also authorise us to process and transmit your personal data in the manner contemplated below in this
Statement of Privacy. For purposes of this Statement of Privacy, “Affiliate” means any member of the Purple Group
Limited group of companies, including without limitation, any subsidiary, sub-subsidiary, holding company, fellow
subsidiary of any holding company of Purple Group Limited.
You authorise Easy Equities to furnish information, which may be protected by data protection legislation, including inter
alia, POPI, regarding your Account and trading history to any person we reasonably determine to be seeking a credit
reference (including other CFD trading companies) in good faith for any lawful purpose.
2.    Collection of your Personal Information
Easy Equities collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or
telephone number. Easy Equities also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as
your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Easy Equities.
This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Website
addresses. This information is used by Easy Equities for the operation of our services, to maintain quality of the services,
for marketing purposes, to provide general statistics regarding use of the Easy Equities Website, for credit control and in
the furtherance of Easy Equities other legitimate interests (including transmission of this information to our Affiliates).
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through
Easy Equities public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Easy Equities does
not read any of your private online communications.
Easy Equities encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Easy Equities so
that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Easy Equities is not responsible for
the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Easy Equities and v family of Websites (including
Websites of our Affiliates).
3.    Use of your Personal Information
Easy Equities collects and uses your personal information to operate the Easy Equities Website and deliver the services
you have requested. Easy Equities also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or
services available from Easy Equities and its affiliates. Easy Equities may also contact you via surveys to conduct
research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Easy Equities does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Easy Equities may, from time to time, contact
you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your
unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.
In addition, Easy Equities may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or
postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your
personal information except to provide these services to Easy Equities, and they are required to maintain the
confidentiality of your information.
Easy Equities does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations,
without your explicit consent.
                                                                                                                              3
 PRIVACY POLICY | MAY 2014

                                                                               [Privacy Policy]
                                                                               [Easy Equities]
Easy Equities keeps track of the Websites and pages our customers visit within Easy Equities, in order to determine
what Easy Equities services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within
Easy Equities to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Easy Equities Websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the
good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the provisions of any law in force from time to time or
comply with legal process served on Easy Equities or the Website; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Easy
Equities; and, (c) to protect the personal safety of users of Easy Equities, or the public.
4.   Use of Cookies
The Easy Equities Website use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is
placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your
computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the
cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is
to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Easy Equities pages, or
register with Easy Equities site or services, a cookie helps Easy Equities to recall your specific information on
subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping
addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Easy Equities Website, the information you previously provided can
be retrieved, so you can easily use the Easy Equities features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually
modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully
experience the interactive features of the Easy Equities services or Websites you visit.
5.   Security of your Personal Information
Easy Equities secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Easy Equities secures the
personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to
other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
6.   Changes to this Statement of Privacy
Easy Equities will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Easy
Equities encourages you to periodically review this Statement of Privacy to be informed of how Easy Equities is
protecting your information.
7.   Contact Information
Easy Equities welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Easy Equities has not
adhered to this Statement, please contact EasyEquities at helpme@easyequities.co.za. We will use commercially
reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
                                                                                                                             4
 PRIVACY POLICY | MAY 2014
